Order	Level	Code	Parent	Description
18347	1	A		Agriculture, hunting and forestry
18348	2	AA	A	Agriculture, hunting and forestry
18349	3	1	AA	Agriculture, hunting and related service activities
18350	4	01.1	1	"Growing of crops; market gardening; horticulture"
18351	5	01.11	01.1	Growing of cereals and other crops n.e.c.
18352	5	01.12	01.1	Growing of vegetables, horticultural specialities and nursery products
18353	5	01.13	01.1	Growing of fruit, nuts, beverage and spice crops
18354	4	01.2	1	Farming of animals
18355	5	01.21	01.2	Farming of cattle, dairy farming
18356	5	01.22	01.2	Farming of sheep, goats, horses, asses, mules and hinnies
18357	5	01.23	01.2	Farming of swine
18358	5	01.24	01.2	Farming of poultry
18359	5	01.25	01.2	Other farming of animals
18360	4	01.3	1	Growing of crops combined with farming of animals (mixed farming)
18361	5	01.30	01.3	Growing of crops combined with farming of animals (mixed farming)
18362	4	01.4	1	"Agricultural and animal husbandry service activities, except veterinary activities; landscape gardening"
18363	5	01.41	01.4	"Agricultural service activities; landscape gardening"
18364	5	01.42	01.4	Animal husbandry service activities, except veterinary activities
18365	4	01.5	1	Hunting, trapping and game propagation, including related service activities
18366	5	01.50	01.5	Hunting, trapping and game propagation, including related service activities
18367	3	2	AA	Forestry, logging and related service activities
18368	4	02.0	2	Forestry, logging and related service activities
18369	5	02.01	02.0	Forestry and logging
18370	5	02.02	02.0	Forestry and logging related service activities
18371	1	B		Fishing
18372	2	BA	B	Fishing
18373	3	5	BA	Fishing,  fish farming and related service activities
18374	4	05.0	5	Fishing,  fish farming and related service activities
18375	5	05.01	05.0	Fishing
18376	5	05.02	05.0	 Fish farming
18377	1	C		Mining and quarrying
18378	2	CA	C	Mining and quarrying of energy producing materials
18379	3	10	CA	"Mining of coal and lignite; extraction of peat"
18380	4	10.1	10	Mining and agglomeration of hard coal
18381	5	10.10	10.1	Mining and agglomeration of hard coal
18382	4	10.2	10	Mining and agglomeration of lignite
18383	5	10.20	10.2	Mining and agglomeration of lignite
18384	4	10.3	10	Extraction and agglomeration of peat
18385	5	10.30	10.3	Extraction and agglomeration of peat
18386	3	11	CA	"Extraction of crude petroleum and natural gas; service activities incidental to oil and gas extraction, excluding surveying"
18387	4	11.1	11	Extraction of crude petroleum and natural gas
18388	5	11.10	11.1	Extraction of crude petroleum and natural gas
18389	4	11.2	11	Service activities incidental to oil and gas extraction, excluding surveying
18390	5	11.20	11.2	Service activities incidental to oil and gas extraction, excluding surveying
18391	3	12	CA	Mining of uranium and thorium ores
18392	4	12.0	12	Mining of uranium and thorium ores
18393	5	12.00	12.0	Mining of uranium and thorium ores
18394	2	CB	C	Mining and quarrying, except of energy producing materials
18395	3	13	CB	Mining of metal ores
18396	4	13.1	13	Mining of iron ores
18397	5	13.10	13.1	Mining of iron ores
18398	4	13.2	13	Mining of non-ferrous metal ores, except uranium and thorium ores
18399	5	13.20	13.2	Mining of non-ferrous metal ores, except uranium and thorium ores
18400	3	14	CB	Other mining and quarrying
18401	4	14.1	14	Quarrying of stone
18402	5	14.11	14.1	Quarrying of  ornamental and building stone
18403	5	14.12	14.1	Quarrying of limestone, gypsum and chalk
18404	5	14.13	14.1	Quarrying of slate
18405	4	14.2	14	Quarrying of sand and clay
18406	5	14.21	14.2	Operation of gravel and sand pits
18407	5	14.22	14.2	Mining of clays and kaolin
18408	4	14.3	14	Mining of chemical and fertilizer minerals
18409	5	14.30	14.3	Mining of chemical and fertilizer minerals
18410	4	14.4	14	Production of salt
18411	5	14.40	14.4	Production of salt
18412	4	14.5	14	Other mining and quarrying n.e.c.
18413	5	14.50	14.5	Other mining and quarrying n.e.c.
18414	1	D		Manufacturing
18415	2	DA	D	Manufacture of food products, beverages and tobacco
18416	3	15	DA	Manufacture of food products and beverages
18417	4	15.1	15	Production, processing and preserving of meat and meat products
18418	5	15.11	15.1	Production and preserving of meat
18419	5	15.12	15.1	Production and preserving of poultrymeat
18420	5	15.13	15.1	Production of meat and poultrymeat products
18421	4	15.2	15	Processing and preserving of fish and fish products
18422	5	15.20	15.2	Processing and preserving of fish and fish products
18423	4	15.3	15	Processing and preserving of fruit and vegetables
18424	5	15.31	15.3	Processing and preserving of potatoes
18425	5	15.32	15.3	Manufacture of fruit and vegetable juice
18426	5	15.33	15.3	Processing and preserving of fruit and vegetables n.e.c.
18427	4	15.4	15	Manufacture of vegetable and animal oils and fats
18428	5	15.41	15.4	Manufacture of crude oils and fats
18429	5	15.42	15.4	Manufacture of refined oils and fats
18430	5	15.43	15.4	Manufacture of margarine and similar edible fats
18431	4	15.5	15	Manufacture of dairy products
18432	5	15.51	15.5	Operation of dairies and cheese making
18433	5	15.52	15.5	Manufacture of ice cream
18434	4	15.6	15	Manufacture of grain mill products, starches and starch products
18435	5	15.61	15.6	Manufacture of grain mill products
18436	5	15.62	15.6	Manufacture of starches and starch products
18437	4	15.7	15	Manufacture of prepared animal feeds
18438	5	15.71	15.7	Manufacture of prepared feeds for farm animals
18439	5	15.72	15.7	Manufacture of prepared pet foods
18440	4	15.8	15	Manufacture of other food products
18441	5	15.81	15.8	"Manufacture of bread; manufacture of fresh pastry goods and cakes"
18442	5	15.82	15.8	"Manufacture of rusks and biscuits; manufacture of preserved pastry goods and cakes"
18443	5	15.83	15.8	Manufacture of sugar
18444	5	15.84	15.8	"Manufacture of cocoa; chocolate and sugar confectionery"
18445	5	15.85	15.8	Manufacture of macaroni, noodles, couscous and similar farinaceous products
18446	5	15.86	15.8	Processing of tea and coffee
18447	5	15.87	15.8	Manufacture of condiments and seasonings
18448	5	15.88	15.8	Manufacture of homogenized food preparations and dietetic food
18449	5	15.89	15.8	Manufacture of other food products n.e.c.
18450	4	15.9	15	Manufacture of beverages
18451	5	15.91	15.9	Manufacture of distilled potable alcoholic beverages
18452	5	15.92	15.9	Production of ethyl alcohol from fermented materials
18453	5	15.93	15.9	Manufacture of wines
18454	5	15.94	15.9	Manufacture of cider and other fruit wines
18455	5	15.95	15.9	Manufacture of other non-distilled fermented beverages
18456	5	15.96	15.9	Manufacture of beer
18457	5	15.97	15.9	Manufacture of malt
18458	5	15.98	15.9	Production of mineral waters and soft drinks
18459	3	16	DA	Manufacture of tobacco products
18460	4	16.0	16	Manufacture of tobacco products
18461	5	16.00	16.0	Manufacture of tobacco products
18462	2	DB	D	Manufacture of textiles and textile products
18463	3	17	DB	Manufacture of textiles
18464	4	17.1	17	Preparation and spinning of textile fibres
18465	5	17.11	17.1	Preparation and spinning of cotton-type fibres
18466	5	17.12	17.1	Preparation and spinning of woollen-type fibres
18467	5	17.13	17.1	Preparation and spinning of worsted-type fibres
18468	5	17.14	17.1	Preparation and spinning of flax-type fibres
18469	5	17.15	17.1	Throwing and preparation of silk, including from noils, and throwing and texturing of synthetic or artificial filament yarns
18470	5	17.16	17.1	Manufacture of sewing threads
18471	5	17.17	17.1	Preparation and spinning of other textile fibres
18472	4	17.2	17	Textile weaving
18473	5	17.21	17.2	Cotton-type weaving
18474	5	17.22	17.2	Woollen-type weaving
18475	5	17.23	17.2	Worsted-type weaving
18476	5	17.24	17.2	Silk-type weaving
18477	5	17.25	17.2	Other textile weaving
18478	4	17.3	17	Finishing of textiles
18479	5	17.30	17.3	Finishing of textiles
18480	4	17.4	17	Manufacture of made-up textile articles, except apparel
18481	5	17.40	17.4	Manufacture of made-up textile articles, except apparel
18482	4	17.5	17	Manufacture of other textiles
18483	5	17.51	17.5	Manufacture of carpets and rugs
18484	5	17.52	17.5	Manufacture of cordage, rope, twine and netting
18485	5	17.53	17.5	Manufacture of non-wovens and articles made from non-wovens, except apparel
18486	5	17.54	17.5	Manufacture of other textiles n.e.c.
18487	4	17.6	17	Manufacture of knitted and crocheted fabrics
18488	5	17.60	17.6	Manufacture of knitted and crocheted fabrics
18489	4	17.7	17	Manufacture of knitted and crocheted articles
18490	5	17.71	17.7	Manufacture of knitted and crocheted hosiery
18491	5	17.72	17.7	Manufacture of knitted and crocheted pullovers, cardigans and similar articles
18492	3	18	DB	"Manufacture of wearing apparel; dressing and dyeing of fur"
18493	4	18.1	18	Manufacture of leather clothes
18494	5	18.10	18.1	Manufacture of leather clothes
18495	4	18.2	18	Manufacture of other wearing apparel and accessories
18496	5	18.21	18.2	Manufacture of workwear
18497	5	18.22	18.2	Manufacture of other outerwear
18498	5	18.23	18.2	Manufacture of underwear
18499	5	18.24	18.2	Manufacture of other wearing apparel and accessories n.e.c.
18500	4	18.3	18	"Dressing and dyeing of fur; manufacture of articles of fur"
18501	5	18.30	18.3	"Dressing and dyeing of fur; manufacture of articles of fur"
18502	2	DC	D	Manufacture of leather and leather products
18503	3	19	DC	"Tanning and dressing of leather; manufacture of luggage, handbags, saddlery, harness and footwear"
18504	4	19.1	19	Tanning and dressing of leather
18505	5	19.10	19.1	Tanning and dressing of leather
18506	4	19.2	19	Manufacture of luggage, handbags and the like, saddlery and harness
18507	5	19.20	19.2	Manufacture of luggage, handbags and the like, saddlery and harness
18508	4	19.3	19	Manufacture of footwear
18509	5	19.30	19.3	Manufacture of footwear
18510	2	DD	D	Manufacture of wood and wood products
18511	3	20	DD	"Manufacture of wood and of products of wood and cork, except furniture; manufacture of articles of straw and plaiting materials"
18512	4	20.1	20	"Sawmilling and planing of wood; impregnation of wood"
18513	5	20.10	20.1	"Sawmilling and planing of wood; impregnation of wood"
18514	4	20.2	20	"Manufacture of veneer sheets; manufacture of plywood, laminboard, particle board, fibre board and other panels and boards"
18515	5	20.20	20.2	"Manufacture of veneer sheets; manufacture of plywood, laminboard, particle board, fibre board and other panels and boards"
18516	4	20.3	20	Manufacture of builders' carpentry and joinery
18517	5	20.30	20.3	Manufacture of builders' carpentry and joinery
18518	4	20.4	20	Manufacture of wooden containers
18519	5	20.40	20.4	Manufacture of wooden containers
18520	4	20.5	20	"Manufacture of other products of wood; manufacture of articles of cork, straw and plaiting materials"
18521	5	20.51	20.5	Manufacture of other products of wood
18522	5	20.52	20.5	Manufacture of articles of cork, straw and plaiting materials
18523	2	DE	D	"Manufacture of pulp, paper and paper products; publishing and printing"
18524	3	21	DE	Manufacture of pulp, paper and paper products
18525	4	21.1	21	Manufacture of pulp, paper and paperboard
18526	5	21.11	21.1	Manufacture of pulp
18527	5	21.12	21.1	Manufacture of paper and paperboard
18528	4	21.2	21	Manufacture of articles of paper and paperboard
18529	5	21.21	21.2	Manufacture of corrugated paper and paperboard and of containers of paper and paperboard
18530	5	21.22	21.2	Manufacture of household and sanitary goods and of toilet requisites
18531	5	21.23	21.2	Manufacture of paper stationery
18532	5	21.24	21.2	Manufacture of wallpaper
18533	5	21.25	21.2	Manufacture of other articles of paper and paperboard n.e.c.
18534	3	22	DE	Publishing, printing and reproduction of recorded media
18535	4	22.1	22	Publishing
18536	5	22.11	22.1	Publishing of books
18537	5	22.12	22.1	Publishing of newspapers
18538	5	22.13	22.1	Publishing of journals and periodicals
18539	5	22.14	22.1	Publishing of sound recordings
18540	5	22.15	22.1	Other publishing
18541	4	22.2	22	Printing and service activities related to printing
18542	5	22.21	22.2	Printing of newspapers
18543	5	22.22	22.2	Printing n.e.c.
18544	5	22.23	22.2	Bookbinding 
18545	5	22.24	22.2	Pre-press activities
18546	5	22.25	22.2	Ancillary activities related to printing
18547	4	22.3	22	Reproduction of recorded media
18548	5	22.31	22.3	Reproduction of sound recording
18549	5	22.32	22.3	Reproduction of video recording
18550	5	22.33	22.3	Reproduction of computer media
18551	2	DF	D	Manufacture of coke, refined petroleum products and nuclear fuel
18552	3	23	DF	Manufacture of coke, refined petroleum products and nuclear fuel
18553	4	23.1	23	Manufacture of coke oven products
18554	5	23.10	23.1	Manufacture of coke oven products
18555	4	23.2	23	Manufacture of refined petroleum products
18556	5	23.20	23.2	Manufacture of refined petroleum products
18557	4	23.3	23	Processing of nuclear fuel
18558	5	23.30	23.3	Processing of nuclear fuel
18559	2	DG	D	Manufacture of chemicals, chemical products and man-made fibres
18560	3	24	DG	Manufacture of chemicals and chemical products
18561	4	24.1	24	Manufacture of basic chemicals
18562	5	24.11	24.1	Manufacture of industrial gases
18563	5	24.12	24.1	Manufacture of dyes and pigments
18564	5	24.13	24.1	Manufacture of other inorganic basic chemicals
18565	5	24.14	24.1	Manufacture of other organic basic chemicals
18566	5	24.15	24.1	Manufacture of fertilizers and nitrogen compounds
18567	5	24.16	24.1	Manufacture of plastics in primary forms
18568	5	24.17	24.1	Manufacture of synthetic rubber in primary forms
18569	4	24.2	24	Manufacture of pesticides and other agro-chemical products
18570	5	24.20	24.2	Manufacture of pesticides and other agro-chemical products
18571	4	24.3	24	Manufacture of paints, varnishes and similar coatings, printing ink and mastics
18572	5	24.30	24.3	Manufacture of paints, varnishes and similar coatings, printing ink and mastics
18573	4	24.4	24	Manufacture of pharmaceuticals, medicinal chemicals and botanical products
18574	5	24.41	24.4	Manufacture of basic pharmaceutical products
18575	5	24.42	24.4	Manufacture of pharmaceutical preparations
18576	4	24.5	24	Manufacture of soap and detergents, cleaning and polishing preparations, perfumes and toilet preparations
18577	5	24.51	24.5	Manufacture of soap and detergents, cleaning and polishing preparations
18578	5	24.52	24.5	Manufacture of perfumes and toilet preparations
18579	4	24.6	24	Manufacture of other chemical products
18580	5	24.61	24.6	Manufacture of explosives
18581	5	24.62	24.6	Manufacture of glues and gelatines
18582	5	24.63	24.6	Manufacture of essential oils
18583	5	24.64	24.6	Manufacture of photographic chemical material
18584	5	24.65	24.6	Manufacture of prepared unrecorded media
18585	5	24.66	24.6	Manufacture of other chemical products n.e.c.
18586	4	24.7	24	Manufacture of man-made fibres
18587	5	24.70	24.7	Manufacture of man-made fibres
18588	2	DH	D	Manufacture of rubber and plastic products
18589	3	25	DH	Manufacture of rubber and plastic products
18590	4	25.1	25	Manufacture of rubber products
18591	5	25.11	25.1	Manufacture of rubber tyres and tubes
18592	5	25.12	25.1	Retreading and rebuilding of rubber tyres
18593	5	25.13	25.1	Manufacture of other rubber products
18594	4	25.2	25	Manufacture of plastic products
18595	5	25.21	25.2	Manufacture of plastic plates, sheets, tubes and profiles
18596	5	25.22	25.2	Manufacture of plastic packing goods
18597	5	25.23	25.2	Manufacture of builders' ware of plastic
18598	5	25.24	25.2	Manufacture of other plastic products
18599	2	DI	D	Manufacture of other non-metallic mineral products
18600	3	26	DI	Manufacture of other non-metallic mineral products
18601	4	26.1	26	Manufacture of glass and glass products
18602	5	26.11	26.1	Manufacture of flat glass
18603	5	26.12	26.1	Shaping and processing of flat glass
18604	5	26.13	26.1	Manufacture of hollow glass
18605	5	26.14	26.1	Manufacture of glass fibres
18606	5	26.15	26.1	Manufacture and processing of other glass, including technical glassware
18607	4	26.2	26	"Manufacture of non-refractory ceramic goods other than for construction purposes; manufacture of refractory ceramic products"
18608	5	26.21	26.2	Manufacture of ceramic household and ornamental articles
18609	5	26.22	26.2	Manufacture of ceramic sanitary fixtures
18610	5	26.23	26.2	Manufacture of ceramic insulators and insulating fittings
18611	5	26.24	26.2	Manufacture of other technical ceramic products
18612	5	26.25	26.2	Manufacture of other ceramic products
18613	5	26.26	26.2	Manufacture of refractory ceramic products
18614	4	26.3	26	Manufacture of ceramic tiles and flags
18615	5	26.30	26.3	Manufacture of ceramic tiles and flags
18616	4	26.4	26	Manufacture of bricks, tiles and construction products, in baked clay
18617	5	26.40	26.4	Manufacture of bricks, tiles and construction products, in baked clay
18618	4	26.5	26	Manufacture of cement, lime and plaster
18619	5	26.51	26.5	Manufacture of cement
18620	5	26.52	26.5	Manufacture of lime
18621	5	26.53	26.5	Manufacture of plaster
18622	4	26.6	26	Manufacture of articles of concrete, plaster and cement
18623	5	26.61	26.6	Manufacture of concrete products for construction purposes
18624	5	26.62	26.6	Manufacture of plaster products for construction purposes
18625	5	26.63	26.6	Manufacture of ready-mixed concrete
18626	5	26.64	26.6	Manufacture of mortars
18627	5	26.65	26.6	Manufacture of fibre cement
18628	5	26.66	26.6	Manufacture of other articles of concrete, plaster and cement
18629	4	26.7	26	Cutting, shaping and finishing of ornamental and building stone
18630	5	26.70	26.7	Cutting, shaping and finishing of ornamental and building stone
18631	4	26.8	26	Manufacture of other non-metallic mineral products
18632	5	26.81	26.8	Production of abrasive products
18633	5	26.82	26.8	Manufacture of other non-metallic mineral products n.e.c.
18634	2	DJ	D	Manufacture of basic metals and fabricated metal products
18635	3	27	DJ	Manufacture of basic metals
18636	4	27.1	27	Manufacture of basic iron and steel and of ferro-alloys 
18637	5	27.10	27.1	Manufacture of basic iron and steel and of ferro-alloys 
18638	4	27.2	27	Manufacture of tubes
18639	5	27.21	27.2	Manufacture of cast iron tubes
18640	5	27.22	27.2	Manufacture of steel tubes
18641	4	27.3	27	Other first processing of iron and steel 
18642	5	27.31	27.3	Cold drawing
18643	5	27.32	27.3	Cold rolling of narrow strip
18644	5	27.33	27.3	Cold forming or folding
18645	5	27.34	27.3	Wire drawing
18646	4	27.4	27	Manufacture of basic precious and non-ferrous metals
18647	5	27.41	27.4	Precious metals production
18648	5	27.42	27.4	Aluminium production
18649	5	27.43	27.4	Lead, zinc and tin production
18650	5	27.44	27.4	Copper production
18651	5	27.45	27.4	Other non-ferrous metal production
18652	4	27.5	27	Casting of metals
18653	5	27.51	27.5	Casting of iron
18654	5	27.52	27.5	Casting of steel
18655	5	27.53	27.5	Casting of light metals
18656	5	27.54	27.5	Casting of other non-ferrous metals
18657	3	28	DJ	Manufacture of fabricated metal products, except machinery and equipment
18658	4	28.1	28	Manufacture of structural metal products
18659	5	28.11	28.1	Manufacture of metal structures and parts of structures
18660	5	28.12	28.1	Manufacture of builders' carpentry and joinery of metal
18661	4	28.2	28	"Manufacture of tanks, reservoirs and containers of metal; manufacture of central heating radiators and boilers"
18662	5	28.21	28.2	Manufacture of tanks, reservoirs and containers of metal
18663	5	28.22	28.2	Manufacture of central heating radiators and boilers
18664	4	28.3	28	Manufacture of steam generators, except central heating hot water boilers
18665	5	28.30	28.3	Manufacture of steam generators, except central heating hot water boilers
18666	4	28.4	28	"Forging, pressing, stamping and roll forming of metal; powder metallurgy"
18667	5	28.40	28.4	"Forging, pressing, stamping and roll forming of metal; powder metallurgy"
18668	4	28.5	28	"Treatment and coating of metals; general mechanical engineering"
18669	5	28.51	28.5	Treatment and coating of metals
18670	5	28.52	28.5	General mechanical engineering
18671	4	28.6	28	Manufacture of cutlery, tools and general hardware
18672	5	28.61	28.6	Manufacture of cutlery
18673	5	28.62	28.6	Manufacture of tools
18674	5	28.63	28.6	Manufacture of locks and hinges
18675	4	28.7	28	Manufacture of other fabricated metal products
18676	5	28.71	28.7	Manufacture of steel drums and similar containers
18677	5	28.72	28.7	Manufacture of light metal packaging
18678	5	28.73	28.7	Manufacture of wire products
18679	5	28.74	28.7	Manufacture of fasteners, screw machine products, chain and springs
18680	5	28.75	28.7	Manufacture of other fabricated metal products n.e.c.
18681	2	DK	D	Manufacture of machinery and equipment n.e.c.
18682	3	29	DK	Manufacture of machinery and equipment n.e.c.
18683	4	29.1	29	Manufacture of machinery for the production and use of mechanical power, except aircraft, vehicle and cycle engines
18684	5	29.11	29.1	Manufacture of engines and turbines, except aircraft, vehicle and cycle engines
18685	5	29.12	29.1	Manufacture of pumps and compressors
18686	5	29.13	29.1	Manufacture of taps and valves
18687	5	29.14	29.1	Manufacture of bearings, gears, gearing and driving elements
18688	4	29.2	29	Manufacture of other general purpose machinery
18689	5	29.21	29.2	Manufacture of furnaces and furnace burners
18690	5	29.22	29.2	Manufacture of lifting and handling equipment
18691	5	29.23	29.2	Manufacture of non-domestic cooling and ventilation equipment
18692	5	29.24	29.2	Manufacture of other general purpose machinery n.e.c.
18693	4	29.3	29	Manufacture of agricultural and forestry machinery
18694	5	29.31	29.3	Manufacture of agricultural tractors
18695	5	29.32	29.3	Manufacture of other agricultural and forestry machinery
18696	4	29.4	29	Manufacture of machine tools
18697	5	29.41	29.4	Manufacture of portable hand held power tools
18698	5	29.42	29.4	Manufacture of other metalworking machine tools
18699	5	29.43	29.4	Manufacture of other machine tools n.e.c.
18700	4	29.5	29	Manufacture of other special purpose machinery
18701	5	29.51	29.5	Manufacture of machinery for metallurgy
18702	5	29.52	29.5	Manufacture of machinery for mining, quarrying and construction
18703	5	29.53	29.5	Manufacture of machinery for food, beverage and tobacco processing
18704	5	29.54	29.5	Manufacture of machinery for textile, apparel and leather production
18705	5	29.55	29.5	Manufacture of machinery for paper and paperboard production
18706	5	29.56	29.5	Manufacture of other special purpose machinery n.e.c.
18707	4	29.6	29	Manufacture of weapons and ammunition
18708	5	29.60	29.6	Manufacture of weapons and ammunition
18709	4	29.7	29	Manufacture of domestic appliances n.e.c.
18710	5	29.71	29.7	Manufacture of electric domestic appliances
18711	5	29.72	29.7	Manufacture of non-electric domestic appliances
18712	2	DL	D	Manufacture of electrical and optical equipment
18713	3	30	DL	Manufacture of office machinery and computers
18714	4	30.0	30	Manufacture of office machinery and computers
18715	5	30.01	30.0	Manufacture of office machinery
18716	5	30.02	30.0	Manufacture of computers and other information processing equipment
18717	3	31	DL	Manufacture of electrical machinery and apparatus n.e.c.
18718	4	31.1	31	Manufacture of electric motors, generators and transformers
18719	5	31.10	31.1	Manufacture of electric motors, generators and transformers
18720	4	31.2	31	Manufacture of electricity distribution and control apparatus
18721	5	31.20	31.2	Manufacture of electricity distribution and control apparatus
18722	4	31.3	31	Manufacture of insulated wire and cable
18723	5	31.30	31.3	Manufacture of insulated wire and cable
18724	4	31.4	31	Manufacture of accumulators, primary cells and primary batteries
18725	5	31.40	31.4	Manufacture of accumulators, primary cells and primary batteries
18726	4	31.5	31	Manufacture of lighting equipment and electric lamps
18727	5	31.50	31.5	Manufacture of lighting equipment and electric lamps
18728	4	31.6	31	Manufacture of electrical equipment n.e.c.
18729	5	31.61	31.6	Manufacture of electrical equipment for engines and vehicles n.e.c.
18730	5	31.62	31.6	Manufacture of other electrical equipment n.e.c.
18731	3	32	DL	Manufacture of radio, television and communication equipment and apparatus
18732	4	32.1	32	Manufacture of electronic valves and tubes and other electronic components
18733	5	32.10	32.1	Manufacture of electronic valves and tubes and other electronic components
18734	4	32.2	32	Manufacture of television and radio transmitters and apparatus for line telephony and line telegraphy
18735	5	32.20	32.2	Manufacture of television and radio transmitters and apparatus for line telephony and line telegraphy
18736	4	32.3	32	Manufacture of television and radio receivers, sound or video recording or reproducing apparatus and associated goods
18737	5	32.30	32.3	Manufacture of television and radio receivers, sound or video recording or reproducing apparatus and associated goods
18738	3	33	DL	Manufacture of medical, precision and optical instruments, watches and clocks
18739	4	33.1	33	Manufacture of medical and surgical equipment and orthopaedic appliances
18740	5	33.10	33.1	Manufacture of medical and surgical equipment and orthopaedic appliances
18741	4	33.2	33	Manufacture of instruments and appliances for measuring, checking, testing, navigating and other purposes, except industrial process control equipment
18742	5	33.20	33.2	Manufacture of instruments and appliances for measuring, checking, testing, navigating and other purposes, except industrial process control equipment
18743	4	33.3	33	Manufacture of industrial process control equipment
18744	5	33.30	33.3	Manufacture of industrial process control equipment
18745	4	33.4	33	Manufacture of optical instruments and photographic equipment
18746	5	33.40	33.4	Manufacture of optical instruments and photographic equipment
18747	4	33.5	33	Manufacture of watches and clocks
18748	5	33.50	33.5	Manufacture of watches and clocks
18749	2	DM	D	Manufacture of transport equipment
18750	3	34	DM	Manufacture of motor vehicles, trailers and semi-trailers
18751	4	34.1	34	Manufacture of motor vehicles
18752	5	34.10	34.1	Manufacture of motor vehicles
18753	4	34.2	34	"Manufacture of bodies (coachwork) for motor vehicles; manufacture of trailers and semi-trailers"
18754	5	34.20	34.2	"Manufacture of bodies (coachwork) for motor vehicles; manufacture of trailers and semi-trailers"
18755	4	34.3	34	Manufacture of parts and accessories for motor vehicles and their engines
18756	5	34.30	34.3	Manufacture of parts and accessories for motor vehicles and their engines
18757	3	35	DM	Manufacture of other transport equipment
18758	4	35.1	35	Building and repairing of ships and boats
18759	5	35.11	35.1	Building and repairing of ships
18760	5	35.12	35.1	Building and repairing of pleasure and sporting boats
18761	4	35.2	35	Manufacture of railway and tramway locomotives and rolling stock
18762	5	35.20	35.2	Manufacture of railway and tramway locomotives and rolling stock
18763	4	35.3	35	Manufacture of aircraft and spacecraft
18764	5	35.30	35.3	Manufacture of aircraft and spacecraft
18765	4	35.4	35	Manufacture of motorcycles and bicycles
18766	5	35.41	35.4	Manufacture of motorcycles
18767	5	35.42	35.4	Manufacture of bicycles
18768	5	35.43	35.4	Manufacture of invalid carriages
18769	4	35.5	35	Manufacture of other transport equipment n.e.c.
18770	5	35.50	35.5	Manufacture of other transport equipment n.e.c.
18771	2	DN	D	Manufacturing n.e.c.
18772	3	36	DN	"Manufacture of furniture; manufacturing n.e.c."
18773	4	36.1	36	Manufacture of furniture
18774	5	36.11	36.1	Manufacture of chairs and seats
18775	5	36.12	36.1	Manufacture of other office and shop furniture
18776	5	36.13	36.1	Manufacture of other kitchen furniture
18777	5	36.14	36.1	Manufacture of other furniture
18778	5	36.15	36.1	Manufacture of mattresses
18779	4	36.2	36	Manufacture of jewellery and related articles
18780	5	36.21	36.2	Striking of coins 
18781	5	36.22	36.2	Manufacture of jewellery and related articles n.e.c.
18782	4	36.3	36	Manufacture of musical instruments
18783	5	36.30	36.3	Manufacture of musical instruments
18784	4	36.4	36	Manufacture of sports goods
18785	5	36.40	36.4	Manufacture of sports goods
18786	4	36.5	36	Manufacture of games and toys
18787	5	36.50	36.5	Manufacture of games and toys
18788	4	36.6	36	Miscellaneous manufacturing n.e.c.
18789	5	36.61	36.6	Manufacture of imitation jewellery
18790	5	36.62	36.6	Manufacture of brooms and brushes
18791	5	36.63	36.6	Other manufacturing n.e.c.
18792	3	37	DN	Recycling
18793	4	37.1	37	Recycling of metal waste and scrap
18794	5	37.10	37.1	Recycling of metal waste and scrap
18795	4	37.2	37	Recycling of non-metal waste and scrap
18796	5	37.20	37.2	Recycling of non-metal waste and scrap
18797	1	E		Electricity, gas and water supply
18798	2	EA	E	Electricity, gas and water supply
18799	3	40	EA	Electricity, gas, steam and hot water supply
18800	4	40.1	40	Production and distribution of electricity
18801	5	40.11	40.1	Production of electricity
18802	5	40.12	40.1	Transmission of electricity
18803	5	40.13	40.1	Distribution and trade of electricity
18804	4	40.2	40	"Manufacture of gas; distribution of gaseous fuels through mains"
18805	5	40.21	40.2	Manufacture of gas
18806	5	40.22	40.2	Distribution and trade of gaseous fuels through mains
18807	4	40.3	40	Steam and hot water supply
18808	5	40.30	40.3	Steam and hot water supply
18809	3	41	EA	Collection, purification and distribution of water
18810	4	41.0	41	Collection, purification and distribution of water
18811	5	41.00	41.0	Collection, purification and distribution of water
18812	1	F		Construction
18813	2	FA	F	Construction
18814	3	45	FA	Construction
18815	4	45.1	45	Site preparation
18816	5	45.11	45.1	"Demolition and wrecking of buildings; earth moving"
18817	5	45.12	45.1	Test drilling and boring
18818	4	45.2	45	"Building of complete constructions or parts thereof; civil engineering"
18819	5	45.21	45.2	General construction of buildings and civil engineering works
18820	5	45.22	45.2	Erection of roof covering and frames
18821	5	45.23	45.2	Construction of motorways, roads, airfields and sport facilities
18822	5	45.24	45.2	Construction of water projects
18823	5	45.25	45.2	Other construction work involving special trades
18824	4	45.3	45	Building installation
18825	5	45.31	45.3	Installation of electrical wiring and fittings
18826	5	45.32	45.3	Insulation work activities
18827	5	45.33	45.3	Plumbing
18828	5	45.34	45.3	Other building installation
18829	4	45.4	45	Building completion
18830	5	45.41	45.4	Plastering
18831	5	45.42	45.4	Joinery installation
18832	5	45.43	45.4	Floor and wall covering
18833	5	45.44	45.4	Painting and glazing
18834	5	45.45	45.4	Other building completion
18835	4	45.5	45	Renting of construction or demolition equipment with operator
18836	5	45.50	45.5	Renting of construction or demolition equipment with operator
18837	1	G		"Wholesale and retail trade; repair of motor vehicles, motorcycles and personal and household goods"
18838	2	GA	G	"Wholesale and retail trade; repair of motor vehicles, motorcycles and personal and household goods"
18839	3	50	GA	"Sale, maintenance and repair of motor vehicles and motorcycles; retail sale of automotive fuel"
18840	4	50.1	50	Sale of motor vehicles
18841	5	50.10	50.1	Sale of motor vehicles
18842	4	50.2	50	Maintenance and repair of motor vehicles
18843	5	50.20	50.2	Maintenance and repair of motor vehicles
18844	4	50.3	50	Sale of motor vehicle parts and accessories
18845	5	50.30	50.3	Sale of motor vehicle parts and accessories
18846	4	50.4	50	Sale, maintenance and repair of motorcycles and related parts and accessories
18847	5	50.40	50.4	Sale, maintenance and repair of motorcycles and related parts and accessories
18848	4	50.5	50	Retail sale of automotive fuel
18849	5	50.50	50.5	Retail sale of automotive fuel
18850	3	51	GA	Wholesale trade and commission trade, except of motor vehicles and motorcycles
18851	4	51.1	51	Wholesale on a fee or contract basis
18852	5	51.11	51.1	Agents involved in the sale of agricultural raw materials, live animals, textile raw materials and semi-finished goods
18853	5	51.12	51.1	Agents involved in the sale of fuels, ores, metals and industrial chemicals
18854	5	51.13	51.1	Agents involved in the sale of timber and building materials
18855	5	51.14	51.1	Agents involved in the sale of machinery, industrial equipment, ships and aircraft
18856	5	51.15	51.1	Agents involved in the sale of furniture, household goods, hardware and ironmongery
18857	5	51.16	51.1	Agents involved in the sale of textiles, clothing, footwear and leather goods
18858	5	51.17	51.1	Agents involved in the sale of food, beverages and tobacco
18859	5	51.18	51.1	Agents specializing in the sale of particular products or ranges of products n.e.c.
18860	5	51.19	51.1	Agents involved in the sale of a variety of goods
18861	4	51.2	51	Wholesale of agricultural raw materials and live animals
18862	5	51.21	51.2	Wholesale of grain, seeds and animal feeds
18863	5	51.22	51.2	Wholesale of flowers and plants
18864	5	51.23	51.2	Wholesale of live animals
18865	5	51.24	51.2	Wholesale of hides, skins and leather
18866	5	51.25	51.2	Wholesale of unmanufactured tobacco
18867	4	51.3	51	Wholesale of food, beverages and tobacco
18868	5	51.31	51.3	Wholesale of fruit and vegetables
18869	5	51.32	51.3	Wholesale of meat and meat products
18870	5	51.33	51.3	Wholesale of dairy produce, eggs and edible oils and fats
18871	5	51.34	51.3	Wholesale of alcoholic and other beverages
18872	5	51.35	51.3	Wholesale of tobacco products
18873	5	51.36	51.3	Wholesale of sugar and chocolate and sugar confectionery
18874	5	51.37	51.3	Wholesale of coffee, tea, cocoa and spices
18875	5	51.38	51.3	Wholesale of other food, including fish, crustaceans and molluscs
18876	5	51.39	51.3	Non-specialized wholesale of food, beverages and tobacco
18877	4	51.4	51	Wholesale of household goods
18878	5	51.41	51.4	Wholesale of textiles
18879	5	51.42	51.4	Wholesale of clothing and footwear
18880	5	51.43	51.4	Wholesale of electrical household appliances and radio and television goods
18881	5	51.44	51.4	Wholesale of china and glassware, wallpaper and cleaning materials
18882	5	51.45	51.4	Wholesale of perfume and cosmetics
18883	5	51.46	51.4	Wholesale of pharmaceutical goods
18884	5	51.47	51.4	Wholesale of other household goods
18885	4	51.5	51	Wholesale of non-agricultural intermediate products, waste and scrap
18886	5	51.51	51.5	Wholesale of solid, liquid and gaseous fuels and related products
18887	5	51.52	51.5	Wholesale of metals and metal ores
18888	5	51.53	51.5	Wholesale of wood, construction materials and sanitary equipment
18889	5	51.54	51.5	Wholesale of hardware, plumbing and heating equipment and supplies
18890	5	51.55	51.5	Wholesale of chemical products
18891	5	51.56	51.5	Wholesale of other intermediate products
18892	5	51.57	51.5	Wholesale of waste and scrap
18893	4	51.8	51	Wholesale of machinery, equipment and supplies
18894	5	51.81	51.8	Wholesale of machine tools
18895	5	51.82	51.8	Wholesale of mining, construction and civil engineering machinery
18896	5	51.83	51.8	Wholesale of machinery for the textile industry and of sewing and knitting machines
18897	5	51.84	51.8	Wholesale of computers, computer peripheral equipment and software
18898	5	51.85	51.8	Wholesale of other office machinery and equipment
18899	5	51.86	51.8	Wholesale of other electronic parts and equipment
18900	5	51.87	51.8	Wholesale of other machinery for use in industry, trade and navigation
18901	5	51.88	51.8	Wholesale of agricultural machinery and accessories and implements, including tractors
18902	4	51.9	51	Other wholesale
18903	5	51.90	51.9	Other wholesale
18904	3	52	GA	"Retail trade, except of motor vehicles and motorcycles; repair of personal and household goods"
18905	4	52.1	52	Retail sale in non-specialized stores
18906	5	52.11	52.1	Retail sale in non-specialized stores with food, beverages or tobacco predominating
18907	5	52.12	52.1	Other retail sale in non-specialized stores
18908	4	52.2	52	Retail sale of food, beverages and tobacco in specialized stores
18909	5	52.21	52.2	Retail sale of fruit and vegetables
18910	5	52.22	52.2	Retail sale of meat and meat products
18911	5	52.23	52.2	Retail sale of fish, crustaceans and molluscs
18912	5	52.24	52.2	Retail sale of bread, cakes, flour confectionery and sugar confectionery
18913	5	52.25	52.2	Retail sale of alcoholic and other beverages
18914	5	52.26	52.2	Retail sale of tobacco products
18915	5	52.27	52.2	Other retail sale of food, beverages and tobacco in specialized stores
18916	4	52.3	52	Retail sale of pharmaceutical and medical goods, cosmetic and toilet articles
18917	5	52.31	52.3	Dispensing chemists
18918	5	52.32	52.3	Retail sale of medical and orthopaedic goods
18919	5	52.33	52.3	Retail sale of cosmetic and toilet articles
18920	4	52.4	52	Other retail sale of new goods in specialized stores
18921	5	52.41	52.4	Retail sale of textiles
18922	5	52.42	52.4	Retail sale of clothing
18923	5	52.43	52.4	Retail sale of footwear and leather goods
18924	5	52.44	52.4	Retail sale of furniture, lighting equipment and household articles n.e.c.
18925	5	52.45	52.4	Retail sale of electrical household appliances and radio and television goods
18926	5	52.46	52.4	Retail sale of hardware, paints and glass
18927	5	52.47	52.4	Retail sale of books, newspapers and stationery
18928	5	52.48	52.4	Other retail sale in specialized stores
18929	4	52.5	52	Retail sale of second-hand goods in stores
18930	5	52.50	52.5	Retail sale of second-hand goods in stores
18931	4	52.6	52	Retail sale not in stores
18932	5	52.61	52.6	Retail sale via mail order houses
18933	5	52.62	52.6	Retail sale via stalls and markets
18934	5	52.63	52.6	Other non-store retail sale
18935	4	52.7	52	Repair of personal and household goods
18936	5	52.71	52.7	Repair of boots, shoes and other articles of leather
18937	5	52.72	52.7	Repair of electrical household goods
18938	5	52.73	52.7	Repair of watches, clocks and jewellery
18939	5	52.74	52.7	Repair n.e.c.
18940	1	H		Hotels and restaurants
18941	2	HA	H	Hotels and restaurants
18942	3	55	HA	Hotels and restaurants
18943	4	55.1	55	Hotels
18944	5	55.10	55.1	Hotels
18945	4	55.2	55	Camping sites and other provision of short-stay accommodation
18946	5	55.21	55.2	Youth hostels and mountain refuges
18947	5	55.22	55.2	Camping sites, including caravan sites
18948	5	55.23	55.2	Other provision of lodgings n.e.c.
18949	4	55.3	55	Restaurants
18950	5	55.30	55.3	Restaurants
18951	4	55.4	55	Bars
18952	5	55.40	55.4	Bars
18953	4	55.5	55	Canteens and catering
18954	5	55.51	55.5	Canteens
18955	5	55.52	55.5	Catering
18956	1	I		Transport, storage and communication
18957	2	IA	I	Transport, storage and communication
18958	3	60	IA	"Land transport; transport via pipelines"
18959	4	60.1	60	Transport via railways
18960	5	60.10	60.1	Transport via railways
18961	4	60.2	60	Other land transport
18962	5	60.21	60.2	Other scheduled passenger land transport
18963	5	60.22	60.2	Taxi operation
18964	5	60.23	60.2	Other land passenger transport
18965	5	60.24	60.2	Freight transport by road
18966	4	60.3	60	Transport via pipelines
18967	5	60.30	60.3	Transport via pipelines
18968	3	61	IA	Water transport
18969	4	61.1	61	Sea and coastal water transport
18970	5	61.10	61.1	Sea and coastal water transport
18971	4	61.2	61	Inland water transport
18972	5	61.20	61.2	Inland water transport
18973	3	62	IA	Air transport
18974	4	62.1	62	Scheduled air transport
18975	5	62.10	62.1	Scheduled air transport
18976	4	62.2	62	Non-scheduled air transport
18977	5	62.20	62.2	Non-scheduled air transport
18978	4	62.3	62	Space transport
18979	5	62.30	62.3	Space transport
18980	3	63	IA	"Supporting and auxiliary transport activities; activities of travel agencies"
18981	4	63.1	63	Cargo handling and storage
18982	5	63.11	63.1	Cargo handling
18983	5	63.12	63.1	Storage and warehousing
18984	4	63.2	63	Other supporting transport activities
18985	5	63.21	63.2	Other supporting land transport activities
18986	5	63.22	63.2	Other supporting water transport activities
18987	5	63.23	63.2	Other supporting air transport activities
18988	4	63.3	63	"Activities of travel agencies and tour operators; tourist assistance activities n.e.c."
18989	5	63.30	63.3	"Activities of travel agencies and tour operators; tourist assistance activities n.e.c."
18990	4	63.4	63	Activities of other transport agencies
18991	5	63.40	63.4	Activities of other transport agencies
18992	3	64	IA	Post and telecommunications
18993	4	64.1	64	Post and courier activities
18994	5	64.11	64.1	National post activities
18995	5	64.12	64.1	Courier activities other than national post activities
18996	4	64.2	64	Telecommunications
18997	5	64.20	64.2	Telecommunications
18998	1	J		Financial intermediation
18999	2	JA	J	Financial intermediation
19000	3	65	JA	Financial intermediation, except insurance and pension funding
19001	4	65.1	65	Monetary intermediation
19002	5	65.11	65.1	Central banking
19003	5	65.12	65.1	Other monetary intermediation
19004	4	65.2	65	Other financial intermediation
19005	5	65.21	65.2	Financial leasing
19006	5	65.22	65.2	Other credit granting
19007	5	65.23	65.2	Other financial intermediation n.e.c.
19008	3	66	JA	Insurance and pension funding, except compulsory social security
19009	4	66.0	66	Insurance and pension funding, except compulsory social security
19010	5	66.01	66.0	Life insurance
19011	5	66.02	66.0	Pension funding
19012	5	66.03	66.0	Non-life insurance
19013	3	67	JA	Activities auxiliary to financial intermediation
19014	4	67.1	67	Activities auxiliary to financial intermediation, except insurance and pension funding
19015	5	67.11	67.1	Administration of financial markets
19016	5	67.12	67.1	Security broking and fund management
19017	5	67.13	67.1	Activities auxiliary to financial intermediation n.e.c.
19018	4	67.2	67	Activities auxiliary to insurance and pension funding
19019	5	67.20	67.2	Activities auxiliary to insurance and pension funding
19020	1	K		Real estate, renting and business activities
19021	2	KA	K	Real estate, renting and business activities
19022	3	70	KA	Real estate activities
19023	4	70.1	70	Real estate activities with own property
19024	5	70.11	70.1	Development and selling of real estate
19025	5	70.12	70.1	Buying and selling of own real estate
19026	4	70.2	70	Letting of own property
19027	5	70.20	70.2	Letting of own property
19028	4	70.3	70	Real estate activities on a fee or contract basis
19029	5	70.31	70.3	Real estate agencies
19030	5	70.32	70.3	Management of real estate on a fee or contract basis
19031	3	71	KA	Renting of machinery and equipment without operator and of personal and household goods
19032	4	71.1	71	Renting of automobiles
19033	5	71.10	71.1	Renting of automobiles
19034	4	71.2	71	Renting of other transport equipment
19035	5	71.21	71.2	Renting of other land transport equipment
19036	5	71.22	71.2	Renting of water transport equipment
19037	5	71.23	71.2	Renting of air transport equipment
19038	4	71.3	71	Renting of other machinery and equipment
19039	5	71.31	71.3	Renting of agricultural machinery and equipment
19040	5	71.32	71.3	Renting of construction and civil engineering machinery and equipment
19041	5	71.33	71.3	Renting of office machinery and equipment, including computers
19042	5	71.34	71.3	Renting of other machinery and equipment n.e.c.
19043	4	71.4	71	Renting of personal and household goods n.e.c.
19044	5	71.40	71.4	Renting of personal and household goods n.e.c.
19045	3	72	KA	Computer and related activities
19046	4	72.1	72	Hardware consultancy
19047	5	72.10	72.1	Hardware consultancy
19048	4	72.2	72	Software consultancy and supply
19049	5	72.21	72.2	Publishing of software
19050	5	72.22	72.2	Other software consultancy and supply
19051	4	72.3	72	Data processing
19052	5	72.30	72.3	Data processing
19053	4	72.4	72	Database activities
19054	5	72.40	72.4	Database activities
19055	4	72.5	72	Maintenance and repair of office, accounting and computing machinery
19056	5	72.50	72.5	Maintenance and repair of office, accounting and computing machinery
19057	4	72.6	72	Other computer related activities
19058	5	72.60	72.6	Other computer related activities
19059	3	73	KA	Research and development
19060	4	73.1	73	Research and experimental development on natural sciences and engineering
19061	5	73.10	73.1	Research and experimental development on natural sciences and engineering
19062	4	73.2	73	Research and experimental development on social sciences and humanities
19063	5	73.20	73.2	Research and experimental development on social sciences and humanities
19064	3	74	KA	Other business activities
19065	4	74.1	74	"Legal, accounting, book-keeping and auditing activities; tax consultancy; market research and public opinion polling; business and management consultancy; holdings"
19066	5	74.11	74.1	Legal activities
19067	5	74.12	74.1	"Accounting, book-keeping and auditing activities; tax consultancy"
19068	5	74.13	74.1	Market research and public opinion polling
19069	5	74.14	74.1	Business and management consultancy activities
19070	5	74.15	74.1	Management activities of holding companies
19071	4	74.2	74	Architectural and engineering activities and related technical consultancy
19072	5	74.20	74.2	Architectural and engineering activities and related technical consultancy
19073	4	74.3	74	Technical testing and analysis
19074	5	74.30	74.3	Technical testing and analysis
19075	4	74.4	74	Advertising
19076	5	74.40	74.4	Advertising
19077	4	74.5	74	Labour recruitment and provision of personnel
19078	5	74.50	74.5	Labour recruitment and provision of personnel
19079	4	74.6	74	Investigation and security activities
19080	5	74.60	74.6	Investigation and security activities
19081	4	74.7	74	Industrial cleaning
19082	5	74.70	74.7	Industrial cleaning
19083	4	74.8	74	Miscellaneous business activities n.e.c.
19084	5	74.81	74.8	Photographic activities
19085	5	74.82	74.8	Packaging activities
19086	5	74.85	74.8	Secretarial and translation activities
19087	5	74.86	74.8	Call centre activities
19088	5	74.87	74.8	Other business activities n.e.c.
19089	1	L		"Public administration and defence; compulsory social security"
19090	2	LA	L	"Public administration and defence; compulsory social security"
19091	3	75	LA	"Public administration and defence; compulsory social security"
19092	4	75.1	75	Administration of the State and the economic and social policy of the community
19093	5	75.11	75.1	General (overall) public service activities
19094	5	75.12	75.1	Regulation of the activities of agencies that provide health care, education, cultural services and other social services, excluding social security
19095	5	75.13	75.1	Regulation of and contribution to more efficient operation of business
19096	5	75.14	75.1	Supporting service activities for the government as a whole
19097	4	75.2	75	Provision of services to the community as a whole
19098	5	75.21	75.2	Foreign affairs
19099	5	75.22	75.2	Defence activities
19100	5	75.23	75.2	Justice and judicial activities
19101	5	75.24	75.2	Public security, law and order activities
19102	5	75.25	75.2	Fire service activities
19103	4	75.3	75	Compulsory social security activities
19104	5	75.30	75.3	Compulsory social security activities
19105	1	M		Education
19106	2	MA	M	Education
19107	3	80	MA	Education
19108	4	80.1	80	Primary education
19109	5	80.10	80.1	Primary education
19110	4	80.2	80	Secondary education
19111	5	80.21	80.2	General secondary education
19112	5	80.22	80.2	Technical and vocational secondary education
19113	4	80.3	80	Higher education
19114	5	80.30	80.3	Higher education
19115	4	80.4	80	Adult and other education
19116	5	80.41	80.4	Driving school activities
19117	5	80.42	80.4	Adult and other education n.e.c.
19118	1	N		Health and social work
19119	2	NA	N	Health and social work
19120	3	85	NA	Health and social work
19121	4	85.1	85	Human health activities
19122	5	85.11	85.1	Hospital activities
19123	5	85.12	85.1	Medical practice activities
19124	5	85.13	85.1	Dental practice activities
19125	5	85.14	85.1	Other human health activities
19126	4	85.2	85	Veterinary activities
19127	5	85.20	85.2	Veterinary activities
19128	4	85.3	85	Social work activities
19129	5	85.31	85.3	Social work activities with accommodation
19130	5	85.32	85.3	Social work activities without accommodation
19131	1	O		Other community, social and personal service activities
19132	2	OA	O	Other community, social and personal service activities
19133	3	90	OA	Sewage and refuse disposal, sanitation and similar activities
19134	4	90.0	90	Sewage and refuse disposal, sanitation and similar activities
19135	5	90.01	90.0	Collection and treatment of sewage
19136	5	90.02	90.0	Collection and treatment of other waste
19137	5	90.03	90.0	Sanitation, remediation and similar activities
19138	3	91	OA	Activities of membership organizations n.e.c.
19139	4	91.1	91	Activities of business, employers' and professional organizations
19140	5	91.11	91.1	Activities of business and employers' organizations
19141	5	91.12	91.1	Activities of professional organizations
19142	4	91.2	91	Activities of trade unions
19143	5	91.20	91.2	Activities of trade unions
19144	4	91.3	91	Activities of other membership organizations
19145	5	91.31	91.3	Activities of religious organizations
19146	5	91.32	91.3	Activities of political organizations
19147	5	91.33	91.3	Activities of other membership organizations n.e.c.
19148	3	92	OA	Recreational, cultural and sporting activities
19149	4	92.1	92	Motion picture and video activities
19150	5	92.11	92.1	Motion picture and video production
19151	5	92.12	92.1	Motion picture and video distribution
19152	5	92.13	92.1	Motion picture projection
19153	4	92.2	92	Radio and television activities
19154	5	92.20	92.2	Radio and television activities
19155	4	92.3	92	Other entertainment activities
19156	5	92.31	92.3	Artistic and literary creation and interpretation
19157	5	92.32	92.3	Operation of arts facilities
19158	5	92.33	92.3	Fair and amusement park activities
19159	5	92.34	92.3	Other entertainment activities n.e.c.
19160	4	92.4	92	News agency activities
19161	5	92.40	92.4	News agency activities
19162	4	92.5	92	Library, archives, museums and other cultural activities
19163	5	92.51	92.5	Library and archives activities
19164	5	92.52	92.5	Museums activities and preservation of historical sites and buildings
19165	5	92.53	92.5	Botanical and zoological gardens and nature reserves activities
19166	4	92.6	92	Sporting activities
19167	5	92.61	92.6	Operation of sports arenas and stadiums
19168	5	92.62	92.6	Other sporting activities
19169	4	92.7	92	Other recreational activities
19170	5	92.71	92.7	Gambling and betting activities
19171	5	92.72	92.7	Other recreational activities n.e.c.
19172	3	93	OA	Other service activities
19173	4	93.0	93	Other service activities
19174	5	93.01	93.0	Washing and dry-cleaning of textile and fur products
19175	5	93.02	93.0	Hairdressing and other beauty treatment
19176	5	93.03	93.0	Funeral and related activities
19177	5	93.04	93.0	Physical well-being activities
19178	5	93.05	93.0	Other service activities n.e.c.
19179	1	P		Activities of households
19180	2	PA	P	Activities of households
19181	3	95	PA	Activities of households as employers of domestic staff
19182	4	95.0	95	Activities of households as employers of domestic staff
19183	5	95.00	95.0	Activities of households as employers of domestic staff
19184	3	96	PA	Undifferentiated goods producing activities of private households for own use
19185	4	96.0	96	Undifferentiated goods producing activities of private households for own use
19186	5	96.00	96.0	Undifferentiated goods producing activities of private households for own use
19187	3	97	PA	Undifferentiated services producing activities of private households for own use
19188	4	97.0	97	Undifferentiated services producing activities of private households for own use
19189	5	97.00	97.0	Undifferentiated services producing activities of private households for own use
19190	1	Q		Extra-territorial organizations and bodies
19191	2	QA	Q	Extra-territorial organizations and bodies
19192	3	99	QA	Extra-territorial organizations and bodies
19193	4	99.0	99	Extra-territorial organizations and bodies
19194	5	99.00	99.0	Extra-territorial organizations and bodies
